

### **Profile**

A third year Interactive Art and Technology student strives to create and improve visual branding and digital experience through human-centred designs. My core competencies are graphics design, sketching, and visualizing content to best serve my users and their needs.

## Skills

Design	Process	Tools
Sketching	Research	Photoshop
Illustration	Ideation	Illustator
Visual Branding	Wireframing	InDesign
Interface Design	Prototyping	Figma
Interaction Design	Testing	XD

## Experience

## **Graphic Designer**

Volunteer - SFU LYFE

September 2021 -Present

#### Illustrator

Freelance - Bonheur

November 2020 -October 2021

#### **Orientation Leader**

Volunteer - Fraser International College

September 2021

- Working in a marketing team of 5 members including VP of Marketing and social media coordinators.
- Designing graphics for social media posts and stories based on the branding guideline by using Photoshop, Illustator and Figma, which increases followers on Instagram.
- Worked as a freelancer for a online clothes shop.
- Communicated with the stakeholder to create visualization for social media posts based on the branding color.
- Created illustration and story highlights for Instagram by using vector on Figma and drawing on Procreate.
- Supported a group of 20 new college students to adapt to the new academic environment by organizing team-building activities to connect them together.
- Operated a campus tour to for the new students which helped them know where to find academic resources or support.

## **Education**

# **Bachelor of Arts, Interactive Arts and Technology Publishing Minor**

Simon Fraser University

January 2021 - Present

## Communication, Art and Technology

Fraser International College

Septermber 2019 - December 2020